A Guide to the Edward H. Peeples, Jr. Papers, n.d., 1915, 1920s-2005
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Miscellaneous audio and visual materials (slides, audio and video recordings, phonographs, photographs), publications, ephemera, and oversize materials. 1930s-2004 (Box 22-36)
  - Friends of Old Time Music, with Clarence Ashley, Dock Boggs, Stanley Brothers, Watson Family, Jesse Fuller, Roscoe Holcomb, Miss. John Hurt, almedia A. Riddle, Hobart Smith, Folkways Production, [phonograph, 33 RPM], n.d. (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Irene and Ellen Kossoy and Erik Darling, Bowling Green and Other Folk Songs From the Southern Mountains, Tradition Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1956 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Mississippi Joe Callicott, Blues Masters Volume 6, Blue Horizon Production, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1968 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Slovenske ljudske pesmi, (Slovene folk songs recorded in 1955-1966 when Slovenia was part of Yugoslavia), [phonograph, 33 RPM], n.d. (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - The Best of Jean Ritchie, Prestige Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], circa early 1960s (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - The Hammer Dulcimer, played by Chet Parker, Folkways Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1966 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Aunt Molly Jackson, Alan Lomax, Library of Congress (recorded 1939), Rounder Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], n.d. (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - American Folk Tales and Songs, with Jean Ritchie, Paul Clayton, and Richard Chase, Tradition Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1956 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Hank Garland, Jazz Winds from a New Direction, Columbia records, [country guitarist turned jazz artist who Peepels knew.], [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - JC Hale and the Blu Fescue, Toss Up, Major Recording Co., Waynesboro, [phonograph, 33 RPM], circa 1970s (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - The East Virginia Toadsuckers, The worst of..., Bill Roper Recording Fan Studio [Richmond, Virginia, members of this group were VCU professors.], [phonograph, 33 RPM], n.d. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - The Dixieland Express, Out of the Rain, recorded at Bias Recording Studio, Springfield, and group from Danville, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Mountain Folk Song Concert Bluegrass Style, with the Stanley Brothers, Carl Story and others, Palace, [includes, according to Peeples, "the riotously funny "My Get Up and Go" (has got up and went) by Jack Campbell"], [phonograph, 33 RPM], circa early 1960s (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - JD Crowe and the Kentucky Mountain Boys, Bluegrass Holiday, King Bluegrass Records, [Peeples used to go see this group in Lexington in the middle 1960s], [phonograph, 33 RPM], circa 1970s (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Instrumental Music of the Southern Appalachians: Banjo, fiddle, Guitar, Dulcimer and Harmonica, Tradition Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1956 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - The Eastern Shores, Southern Journey 8, Alan Lomax, Library of Congress, Prestige Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1959, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Southern White Spirituals, Southern Journey 11, Alan Lomax, Library of Congress, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1959, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - The Winding Creek Bluegrass Boys, Under Your Spell Again, recorded at Wally Cleaver's Recording Studio, Fredericksburg, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - The Carter Family, 'Mid the Green Fields of Virginia, RCA, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1963 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Woody Guthrie Sings Folk songs with Leadbelly, Cisco Houston, Sonny Terry, Bess Hawes; Folkways Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1962 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Paul Robeson: American Ballader, Everest Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1977 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - 50 Years of Bluegrass Hits Volume 1, CMH Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Lester Flatt and Earl Scruggs and the Foggy Mountain Boys, Foggy Mountain Banjo, Columbia Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], circa early 1960s (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Lester Flatt and Earl Scruggs and the Foggy Mountain Boys, Flatt and Scruggs at Carnegie Hall, Columbia Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1963 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lester Flatt, The Best of Lester Flatt, RCA Victor Records, [phonograph, 33 RPM], 1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - The 1968 Annual Report of the American Economic Foundation. 1968 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The 1989 Virginia Youth Survey. City of Richmond's Youth Services Commission, October 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - American Academy of Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation. Official Program from 39th Annual Assembly. November 1-4, 1977. 1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Moreland, J. Kenneth. Racial Attitudes and Racial Balance in public Schools: A Case Study of Lynchburg, Virginia. U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare, October 1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Buckley, Silma. Islamic Parenting: The Natural Alternative. Moslem Convert's Association of Singapore, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Capital Area Comprehensive Health Planning Council Inc. H ealth Study Model Neighborhood Area. 1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Center to Prevent Handgun Violence. Caught in the Crossfire: A Report on Handgun Violence in Our Nation's Schools. Washington, D.C., September 1990. 1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Citizens' Council Publications, 1950s, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - City of Richmond Urban Violence Strategy "A Safe Neighborhood Initiative." Fifth Draft, July 1991. 1991 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Cogan, Lee. Negroes for Medicine. Baltimore: Johns Hopkins Press, 1968. 1968 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Clark, Paul. Let Understand the Negro. Mississippi. n.d. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Darlington, C.D. The Control of Evolution in Man. Reprinted from The Eugenics Review. Vol.50, No. 3, October 1958. 1958 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Darsh, S.M. Islamic Health Rules. Ta-Ha Publishers: London, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - The Doctor-Patient Relationship in the Changing Health Scene. Ed. Gallagher, DHEW Publication No. (NIH) 78-183. U.S. Government Printing Office: Washington, D.C., 1978 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Doi, Abdul Rahman I. Women in the Qur'an and the Sunnah. Ta-Ha Publishers: London, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Domestic Violence: A Directory of Protocols for Health care Providers. Children's Safety Network, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Eastland, James O. Is the Supreme Court Communist? Here are the Facts as Disclosed by United States Senator James O. Eastland. n.d. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Emotional Aspects of School Desegregation: A Report by Psychiatrists. Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry, New York, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - The Family Pages: A directory of Virginia organizations dedicated to the prevention And treatment of family violence. FACT, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - The Figgie Report on fear of Crime Part III: A Fourteen City Profile. Figgie International, Inc.: Ohio. n.d. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - First Ross Roundtable. Family Violence. Ross Laboratories: Ohio, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Gabriel's Rebellion. Henrico County Historic Preservation and Museum Services. n.d. (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Gabriel's Rebellion. Henrico County Historic Preservation and Museum Services. n.d. (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - George, Wesley Critz. The Biology of the Race Problem. Commissioner of the Governor of Alabama, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Greenberg, David F. The Problem of Prisons. National Peace Literature Service: Philadelphia. n.d. (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Greenfield, Lawrence A. Alcohol and Crime. Bureau of Justice Statistics: Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Gregor, James A. On the Nature of Prejudice. Reprinted from The Eugenics Review. Vol. 52, No. 4, January 1961. 1961 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Gundy, Judy K. Domestic Violence: The Role of the Medical Practitioner. n.d. (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - RESOLUTIONS: Domestic Violence Prevention Project: Richmond. n.d. (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Haag, Ernest van den. Social Science Testimony in the Desegregation Cases - A Reply to Professor Kenneth Clark. Reprinted from Villanova Law Review. Vol. 6, No. 1, Fall 1960. 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Hall, E. Raymond. Zoological Subspecies of Man. Reprinted from The Mankind Quarterly. Vol. 1, No. 2, October 1960 1960 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Handbook for Community Fact Finders. American Friends Service Committee: Philadelphia, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Handbook of School Health Problems. PAIDEIA Course in School Health, Virginia Commonwealth University, Spring 1974. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Hanna, Diane. Health Risk Appraisal and Health Promotion in Young Adults. Richmond: Virginia Commonwealth University, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Henley, David A. Existential Phenomenology: Experimental Approach to Sociological Inquiry. Undergraduate Paper: Spring Semester, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Hildebrand, George H. Poverty, Income Maintenance, and the Negative Income Tax. Cornell University: New York, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies. The Black Community and Revenue Sharing. Washington, D.C., January 1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - The Journal of Nursing Education. Vol. 7, No. 3, August 1968. 1968 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Keller, Suzanne. Beyond the Ruling Class: Strategic Elites in Modern Society. Random House: New York, 1968. 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Kotz, Nick. Let Them Eat Promises: The Politics of Hunger in the United States. Anchor Books: New York, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Lundberg, George A. and Lenore Dickson. Selective Association of Ethnic Groups in a High School. The International Association for the Advancement of Ethnology And Eugenics: New York, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Man and the Economy: The Social Implications of Economic Patterns. American Friends Service Committee, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Medicine in the Ghetto. Ed. John C. Norman. Meredith Corporation: New York, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan Universities. Vol. 6, No. 2, Fall 1995. 1995 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Minority Responses: Comparative Views of Reactions to Subordination. Ed. Minako Kurkowa. Random House; New York, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Minuchin, Salvadore, Braulio Montalvo, Bernard G. Guerney, Jr., Bernice L. Roseman, And Florence Schumer. Families of the Slums: An Exploration of Their Function Treatment. Basic Books, Inc.: New York, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Moreland, J. Kenneth. Kent Revisited: Blue Collar Aspirations and Achievements. Reprinted from Blue Collar World: Studies of the American Worker. Prentice Hall: Englewood Cliffs, 1964. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Moreland, J. Kenneth. R acial Attitudes and Racial Balance in public Schools: A Case Study of Lynchburg, Virginia. U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare, October 1976 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - National School Safety Center. Gangs in Schools: Breaking Up is Hard to Do. Pepperdine University Press: Malibu, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - The New Yorker. March 13, 1971. 1971 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - The New Yorker. March 20, 1971. 1971 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Nursing Forum. Vol. VII, No. 1. 1968 [includes co-authored article by Peeples, "Social-Psychological Obstacles to Effective Health Team Practice] 1968 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Peeples, Edward. "Stroke Epidemiology: Current State of Affairs in Virginia". Draft, September 1977. 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Policy Statement on Income Maintenance, National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, New York, 1972. 1972 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Poll, Solomon. Racial Integration in a Metropolitan Presbytery. Albert M. Greenfield Center for Human Relations, University of Pennsylvania, 1963. 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Porteus, Stanley. Ethnic Group Differences. Reprinted from The Mankind Quarterly. Vol. 1, No. 3, January 1961. 1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Preventing Violence in Contra Costa County: A Countywide Action Plan and A Framework for Action. CCC Health Services Department, Prevention Program, August 1994. 1994 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Protecting Working Teens. August 1995. 1995 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Prothrow-Stith, Deborah. Violence Prevention Curriculum for Adolescents. Educational Development Center, 1987 1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Puryear, Paul L. Black and Minority Health Issues in Virginia. The University of Virginia Newsletter. Vol. 69, No. 4, May/June 1993. 1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Racial Violence in the United States. Ed. Allen Grimshaw. Aldine Publishing Company: Chicago, 1969. 1969 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Randall-David, Elizabeth. Strategies for Working with Culturally Diverse Communities and Clients. Washington, D.C. 1989. 1989 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Raven's Guide to AIDS Prevention Resources. Alaska Native Health Board and National Native American AIDS Prevention Center, January 1991. 1991 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Reade, Alison. Statewide Childhood Injury Prevention Plan. Virginia Department OF Health, September 1990. 1990 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Responding to Domestic Violence in Virginia: A Directory of Service Programs. Virginians Against Domestic Violence (VADV). May 14, 1993. 1993 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Richmond Violence Prevention Forum: Sharing Solutions. Richmond Violence Prevention and Intervention Services, June 1990. 1990 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Rosenkranz, Otto H. Interstate Migration of the Native White Population and Native Non-White Population According to the United States Census of 1950-1940-1930 Mississippi. Sexual Assault Crisis Centers in Virginia. Virginians Aligned Against Sexual Assault (VAASA): Charlottesville, FY 1994 1994 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Sexual Assault Crisis Centers in Virginia. Virginians Aligned Against Sexual Assault (VAASA): Charlottesville, FY 1996. 1996 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - School Safety. National School Safety Center Newsjournal. Fall 1987. 1987 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Sixth National Conference of Friends on Race Relations. Black Mountain, N.C., July 6-9, 1967 1967 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - "Social and Human Needs Task Force Richmond Tomorrow." Draft Report. n.d. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - South African Panorama. South Africa, March 1965. 1965 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Southern Cultures, Vol. 1, No. 2, Winter 1995 (includes a conversation with Kenneth and Margaret Moreland). 1965 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Southern Exposure. Vol. XIII, No. 4, July/August 1985. 1985 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Southern Exposure. Vol. XIII, No. 5, September/October 1985. 1985 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Suttles, Gerald D. The Social Order of the Slum: Ethnicity and Territory in the Inner City. University of Chicago Press: Chicago, 1968. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Thomas, Alexander and Samuel Sillen. Racism and Psychiatry. Brunner/Mazel, Inc.: New York, 1972. 1972 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Tolson, Donna J. Increased Immigration for Virginia: An Asset for Virginia. n.d. (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - The Virginia Newsletter: University of Virginia. Vol. 73, No. 3, April 1997. 1997 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - U.S. Congress. Joint Economic Committee. The Economics of Federal Subsidy Programs. 92nd Congress, 2nd session, May 8, 1972. 1972 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - U.S. Congress. Joint Economic Committee. The American Distribution of Income: A Structural Problem. 92nd Congress, 2nd session, March 17, 1972. 1972 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - U.S. Congress. Joint Economic Committee. Impact of the Property Tax: Its Implications for Urban Problems. 9oth Congress, 2nd session, May 1968. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - U.S. Department of Justice. Violence by Intimates. NCJ-167237, March 1998. 1998 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Violence and Victims. Vol. 8, No. 3, Fall 1993. 1993 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Violence in the Community Issues, Solutions, and Responsibilities. Training, November 6-9, 1994. 1994 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Violence in Schools: Recommendations for Action by the Educational Summit. Charlottesville: October 1992. 1992 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Violence Prevention Forum Proceedings. Richmond, June 15, 1989. 1989 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Violence Prevention Project. A List of Optimum Data Elements. January 1995. 1995 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Department of Criminal Justice Services. Violent Crimes in Convenience Stores: Analysis of Crimes, Criminals and Costs. House Document No. 30, Richmond, 1993. 1993 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Virginia Department of Education. 1993 Virginia High School Youth Risk Behavior Survey Report. January 1994. 1994 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Virginia Department of Education. 1993 Virginia High School Youth Risk Behavior Survey Report. January 1994. (Draft) 1994 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Virginia Department of Health. Report of the Virginia Department of the Statistical Profile of Women's Health Status in Virginia. House Document No. 82, Richmond, 1994. 1994 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Virginia Department of Health. Women's Health Status in Virginia. House Document No. 53. Richmond, 1995. 1995 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Welch, Robert. Danger for the Doctors. John Birch Society, 1970. 1970 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Welcome to Council School: A Handbook of Information and School Policy. Council School Foundation: Jackson, Mississippi, 1970. 1970 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Wilcox County, Alabama - A Study of Social, Economic, and Educational Bankruptcy, National Education Association, Commission on Professional Rights and Responsibilities, June 1967 1967 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Women Against Violence. Stop the Violence. Volume 1. n.d. (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Women Vs. Violence. Women's International League for Peace and Freedom. Virginia Union University, October 30, 1990. 1990 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Working Together To Stop the Violence: A Blueprint for Safer Communities. National Crime Prevention Council: Washington, D.C., October 1994. 1994 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Youth Violence Locating and Using Data. March 1996. 1996 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Audio Tape - ABC News - Peeples, December 1975 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Audio Tape - All Things Considered (National Public Radio) - Peeples on Multiculturalism and Euthanasia, 1991 1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Audio Tape - All Things Considered (National Public Radio) - Peeples on Behavioral; Medicine, 1988. 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Audio Tape - All Things Considered (National Public Radio) - Peeples on Behavioral; Medicine, 1988. 1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Audio Tape - Edward Peeples, interview by Amy Dail (student at Governor's School), Nov. 29, 2002 2002 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Audio Tape - Hurricane Camille - Damage in Mississippi (3 tapes), 1969 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Audio Tape - NBC Today Show - Peeples with Hugh Downs - Damage to Mississippi from Camille, 1969 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Audio Tape - "Recognizing our Multiplicities" by Peggy McIntosh, January 1991 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Audio Tape - Stephanie Pyle Noon Show (WCVE) Peeples on Violence (2 tapes), June 1990 1990 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Audio Tape - Bus Lecture by Peeples (University of Kentucky), 1967 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Audio Tape - American Friends Service Committee - Peeples on Hurricane Stricken Area of Mississippi, October 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Audio Tape - "Conditions in Virginia Prisons" by Philip Hirschkop, April 1969 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Audio Tape - Video on Curacao Museum (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Video tape - "Beyond Hate" - Bill Moyers, May 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Video tape - "Black/White Issues: Overcoming Barriers to Effective Service" (School of Social Work Teleconference), June 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Video tape - "Encampment for Citizenship", c. 1994 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Video tape - "Impact of Violence", October 1991 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Video tape - Improved Social Service Delivery to Minority Children and Families (Teleconference Series), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Video tape - "Family System Dynamics", February 1990 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Video tape - "The Black Family", April 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Video tape - "The Hispanic Family", April 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Video tape - "The Southeast Asian Family" August 1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Video tape - MacNeil Lehrer News Hour Series, June 17-21, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Video tape - NBC News Special Summer Showcase, August 1988 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Political buttons and Col. Oliver North playing cards n.d., 1960s-1990s (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - Air Views, Ed's Flight, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - Anti-Apartheid, New York City, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - Appalachia, Kentucky and Virginia, n.d., 1966 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - Bear, Smoketown and Lancaster, PA, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - Byrd Park Flagpole, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - Charles Dickens and the University of St. Andrews, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - Charlie Carleton, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - Church, Amelia County, Virginia, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - Civil Rights Honor VFH, Dinner and Conference, Charlottesvile 2004 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - Commonwealth Club, Richmond, Virginia 1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - Confederate camp - Amelia Co., Virginia, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Photographs - Confederate chapel - Viginia Museum of Fine Arts, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Photographs - Confederate flags at Chapel - Viginia Museum of Fine Arts, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Photographs - Confederate flag - Tangier, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - Confederate flag on TV, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - Confederate sites in Richmond and Virginia, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Photographs - Corley House, Mary and Karl n.d. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Photographs - Dr. R. Walter Marshall Memorial, Tennis Courts, Lynchburg, VA 2004 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Photographs - Declaration of Independence from Violence, Richmond, Virginia (composed by Peeples), 1990 1990 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - Eastern Shore, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - Eastern Shore, Bayview Community Health Center n.d. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - Eastern Shore, Blue Crab Bay Co., 2002 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - Eastern Shore, Cape Charles, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - Eastern Shore, Poverty and Housing, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - Eastern Shore, Town Meeting, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - Eastern Shore, Wachapreague n.d. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - Edward Peeples photos, CD 1 n.d. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - Florida Bay, Titusviulle, Florida, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - Gabriel's Revolt, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - Gloucester Co., n.d. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Photographs - "Good News" photos, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Photographs - Greaves Mountain Farm, tree, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Photographs - Hanover Coounty, Virginia - Hispanics picking tomatoes, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - Hobo sites, campfire, 1970s (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - Hurricane Isabel, September 2003 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Photographs - Libby Hill, Confederate soldiers monument, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Photographs - Madison Co., 2000 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Photographs - MCV Hospital door (Broad St./Southside), April 2003 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - Minnesota and Iowa Scenes, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Photographs - New Mexico postcards, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Photographs - Old abandoned Todd building, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - Old Spring Street, Virginia State Penitentiary, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - Parson's House, Jacob's House, Richmond, Virginia, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - Peebles St. and nearby sites, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - Police on horseback, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - Political graffiti, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - Poor house on US 460 n.d. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - Poverty on Eastern Shore, Virginia, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - Poverty in Kentucky, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 9)